Tristan Scott

500 Webster Rd. Lot #342 | Auburn, AL | 256-493-0366 | me@tristan-scott.com

SUMMARY

Upcoming Software Engineering graduate from Auburn University with over two years of full stack web development experience. A fast learner with a friendly demeanor, a passion for problem solving, and a constant desire to learn new skills. Looking to join a skilled development team and kickstart a career in software development.

EDUCATION

Auburn University | Auburn, AL

Bachelor of Software Engineering | May 2020

- SOA Founders Scholarship Recipient
- Dean's List Spring 2016

EXPERIENCE

Unconfusing Technology | Auburn, AL

Engineering Co-op | June 2017 – September 2019

- Developed full stack websites using PHP, HTML, CSS, SQL and JS
- Consulted on-site and remote technical support
- Directed IT and software development projects

Academy Sports | Auburn, AL

Sales Associate | February 2016 – May 2017

- Communicated with customers to fulfill footwear needs
- Maintained a well-organized department
- Coordinated with footwear team to meet sales goals

TGL Communications | Auburn, AL

IT Internship | August 2015 – December 2015

- Provided tech support for offices and manufacturing plants
- Monitored servers, firewalls, and other critical systems
- Ensured accurate and rapid service according to SLA

PROJECTS

Watson Pizza | In Progress

Currently working as part of a four-member team on a virtual agent pizza ordering system using IBM's Watson assistant. Working with an IBM sponsor to setup web services that allow Watson to take pizza orders over telephone.

TIA REST API | September 2017 – November 2017

Spearheaded development of REST API for the Transportation Intermediaries Association online data collection web application as part of Co-op capstone project.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, C++, Python, PHP, JavaScript, SQL

Frameworks: CodeIgniter, Materialize, Bootstrap, JQuery, Swing, Junit, Flask

API: Google Maps, AWS, IBM Watson, RESTful Development

Platforms: Windows, MacOS, Linux

Networking: Systems Administration, LAN Installation, LAN Configuration

Leadership: Project Management, Communication, Problem Solving

Other: Technical Documentation, UML Diagramming, Git